[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are badgers the largest native carnivores found in the UK?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Police song does Reggie Hammond sing while he is in prison in the movie 48 Hrs.?", "correct_answer": "Roxanne", "incorrect_answers": ["Walking on The Moon", "Every Breath You Take", "Message in a Bottle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the idiomatic phrase to have a sweet tooth?", "correct_answer": "To be addicted to sweets", "incorrect_answers": ["To be excessively sentimental", "To be meek and humble", "To be talkative and eloquent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sound travels more swiftly through air than through steel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These compounds are emitted by plants and form gasses, which can be smelled.", "correct_answer": "Aromatics", "incorrect_answers": ["Vapors", "Odors", "Oils"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Fujita scale rates a tornados intensity by the damage it inflicts on human-built structures, this scale classifies hurricanes by the intensity of their sustained winds.", "correct_answer": "Saffir-Simpson scale", "incorrect_answers": ["Beaufort scale", "Kardashev scale", "Hamilton-Norwood scale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cat breed occurred naturally, most probably in Egypt. It has silky short fur with special ticked coloration.", "correct_answer": "Abyssinian", "incorrect_answers": ["Korat", "Sphynx", "Burmilla"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tim Matheson, famous for playing Otter in the 1978 comedy Animal House, voiced which one of these cartoon characters?", "correct_answer": "Jace in Space Ghost", "incorrect_answers": ["Boo-Boo in Yogi Bear", "Zandor in The Herculoids", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these equations can describe the Theorem of Pythagoras?", "correct_answer": "a^2+b^2=c^2", "incorrect_answers": ["sqrt(pi)=t^3", "e^(pi*i)=-1", "a^3+b^3=c^3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these cartoon characters is Bugs Bunnys rival?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Martian Marvin", "Yosemite Sam", "Elmer Fudd"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these statements about aardvarks is false?", "correct_answer": "Aardvarks only eat termites.", "incorrect_answers": ["Aardvarks are hunted for meat.", "Aardvarks are color blind.", "Aardvarks are nocturnal."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Geckos have immovable eyelids and cant blink. How do they keep their eyes clean?", "correct_answer": "They lick their own eyes.", "incorrect_answers": ["A tiny insect lives under their eyelids and cleans their eyes.", "They dip their eyes in water.", "They cover their eyes with their toes."]}]